Sagiri, got a minute?
I have to talk to you about tomorrow.
What is it?
S-Sagiri?
That outfit...
A yukata.
What's the occasion?
Because...
You want to go see the fireworks?
Th-That's not it!
I can't go outside, so...
Onii-san?
What are you thinking about?
Just how cute you are in that yukata.
Really?
How to put it...
You kind of look like Muramasa-senpai.
Nii-san, what did you just say?
Umm...
How cute you are in that yukata.
And how you kind of look like
Muramasa-senpai.
See, she usually wears kimonos and stuff.
And she's really pretty!
So, I mean, you're just as much...
Anyway, she confessed her love to you, right?
How'd you know that?
I can tell as much.
She's just like you, Nii-san.
She confessed in the same way you did, right?
But I don't know your reply to her.
I turned her down.
I said I was in love with someone.
I see.
Right. Is that so.
I-It's not like I asked
because I was interested or anything.
I see.
How do you feel about her right now?
How?
Of course, I like her.
Huh? You said you turned her down!
I did turn her down.
But she said my novels were
the most interesting in the world.
It was the first time someone told me that.
So I've gotten to like her a lot.
- How much?
- What?
How much do you like her?
W-Well, about second in the world?
Wh-Who is first?
That's...
Who? Say it. Hurry up.
Well...
You.
Ni-Nii-san, why do you say stuff like that?
Just because I'm turned down doesn't mean
my love is going to suddenly change.
But that's not—
Or rather, Sagiri...
Why are you wearing that yukata?
Idiot!
ヒトリゴト だ よ 恥ずかしい こと 聞かないで よ ね
Hitorigoto     da  yo    Hazukashii    Koto      Kikanaide     yo ne
I'm just mumbling to myself... don't ask me something so embarrassing!
キミノコトだよで もその先は　    言わないけどね
Kimi no Koto da yo Demo Sono Saki wa        Iwanai     kedo ne
It's about you... but I won't tell you any more than that!
Nii-sama subs presents:
掛け違えてる　ボタンみたいなもどかしさを
Kakechigaeteru      Botan    Mitaina       Modokashisawo
I'm so mixed up, like my buttons have been switched around.
ほどけないまま   また難しくしようとしてる
Hodokenaimama     Mata Muzukashiku Shiyou Toshiteru
Unable to figure it out, I'm just making things difficult again.
伝えたい  気持ちは 今日も
Tsutaetai     Kimochi wa Kyou mo
Once again, the feeling I want to tell you
言葉になる直前に　    変換ミスの連続で
Kotoba ni Naru Chokuzen ni  　Henkan Misuno Renzokude
Suffers a series of typos before it can even become words.
ため息と一緒に飲みこんだら　ほろ苦い…
}Tameiki  to Issho ni   Nomikondara　     Horonigai…
When I drink them down, along with my sighs, they taste so bitter..
ふとしたときに　探しているよ, 君の笑顔を　探しているよ
Futoshita Toki ni        Sagashiteiruyo,    Kimino Egao wo   Sagashiteiru yo
I'm searching before I even realize, I'm searching for your smile!
無意識の中　その理由は　まだ言えないけど
MuishikinoNaka　  Sono Riyuu wa       Mada Ienai Kedo
It happens unconsciously so I can't even tell you the reason why!
ひとりでいると　会いたくなるよ, 誰といたって　会いたくなるよ
Hitori     de  Iru   to　       Aitaku   naru  yo,   Dare to Itatte       　Aitaku     Naru  yo
Whenever I'm alone, I start wanting to see you! No matter who I'm with, I start wanting to see you!
たった一言　ねえどうして?
Tatta Hitokoto       Nee Doushite?
It's just one single phrase, so why is it...?
Aah 言えないその言葉　言えないこの気持ち　Aah
Aah...     Ienai    Sono Kotoba     　Ienai       Kono Kimochi   　Aah
Ahh... I can't say the words! I can't tell you this feeling! Ahh...
早く   気づいてほしいのに
Hayaku,        Kizuitehoshii      no ni
I just wish you'd hurry up and realize!
I'll be going now!
Sagiri, are you awake?
I'll be sleeping over
at the editorial office tomorrow.
You know, work for the upcoming book.
It's crunch time.
I'll leave your food in the fridge,
so make sure to eat.
And, if you need anything, call me right away.
I'll come back home.
And—
I know! You're too overprotective!
Are you still angry?
I'm not a kid. I'll be all right!
Take care, Nii-san.
And now, I will commence home security!
Okay!
I have secured the safety
of my home tod—
Izumi-san! Are you not home?
It's him. How dare he surprise me?
Hurry up and get out of here.
Sorry we missed you!
To: Sagiri Izumi
We attempted to deliver,
but resident was not home.
From: Amu Amu
Wh...
What?
Figures from:
Legend of the Illusionary Demon Sword
Nii-san, hurry home!
I'm so looking forward to it!
I wonder if that guy
will be there again this year.
I wonder if Sagiri is all right.
I'm here in Chiba City right now!
Today in Chiba City,
the Civilian Fireworks Festival will be held.
Many people are here to celebrate!
Now, I'd like to interview people on the street.
I'm here with my family to see the fireworks!
I hope I can come here
with a boyfriend next year!
Are you her older sister?
Y-Yes.
You have a cute younger sister!
I'm currently looking
for a handsome boyfriend!
Come now, be quiet!
I'm not jealous or anything.
Those sisters really do get along.
Now, back to you in the studio!
You can use this place as much as you want.
Good luck with turning it into a long novel!
When you're done,
please hand it over to the part-timer.
Well, do your best! See you!
You're going home?
No check-throughs?
I'll do it tomorrow!
How cute you are in that yukata...
You kind of look like Muramasa-senpai.
That's it, but that's not it.
That's not it!
What's wrong, Nii-san?
Yeah.
Did you eat your meal?
You called just to ask me that?
I told you I'd be all right.
Well...
What's wrong?
Nothing. Don't stay up too late.
Yup. Good luck with your work, too.
Such a weird Nii-san.
Sorry we missed you!
I forgot to tell him.
Masamune!
What are you thinking about
with a serious look on your face?
I think Sagiri wants to go
to the fireworks festival.
I was thinking if I could do something about it.
- Siscon.
- Shut up!
More like, what's with that outfit?
This?
That.
I'm cute, aren't I?
Did you go to supplementary class
so you can get enough attendance days?
No way!
I came over here to flaunt
how lovely I look in my school uniform.
How do I look? A lot more charming
than someone like Muramasa, right?
You've been working this entire time?
I just finished up and heading back home.
Sheesh. So that's why
you didn't answer the phone.
Oh well. I have a message for you.
From who?
Shidou Kunimitsu.
The rookie author who lost against you
in the Light-novel Tenkaichi Budoukai.
A wrap party, huh?
I got an invite from a Twitter DM.
I was hoping we can have it at your place,
with me and Eromanga-sensei there too.
That's fine, right?
Shidou-sensei is okay with it?
After all, he missed getting published
because I won.
About that. Apparently, his story
is going to be published anyway.
What?
In the end, they decided to publish
up to the "third-place piece" as books.
H-Hold on a second! I thought they didn't have
the luxury of increasing publishing slots?
There were more slots?
"We increased it because I did my best!
Winning or losing shouldn't matter.
In the end, you have to publish
interesting works!"
And such. I mean, that's something
your editor would totally say, right?
But their release dates are going to be
pretty far off in the future.
You wouldn't have been able
to continue being an author like that, right?
If that's the case, it's not like Shidou-sensei
has a grudge against me or anything.
Problems all solved?
No, there's still one.
Well...
Seeing Muramasa-senpai would be, um...
You dumped her, right?
I see, so she might feel awkward
and may not want to see you.
That's what you're thinking, right?
How stupid to worry over
something that may or may not be!
One chat settles it for sure,
so why don't you talk to her?
You're really amazing at stuff like that.
I'll try it.
Thanks.
More like, what's wrong?
You're rather honest today.
Have you fallen in love with Elf-sensei?
I have not.
But...
I thought it'd be great
if you were my older sister.
Ouch!
I don't need a little brother like you.
Idiot.
Change your look for the summer!
Are you ready for hot summer dates?
You won't be watching
the fireworks alone, right!?
I don't get it.
Yes, yes. Yes.
Then, I'll put her on.
Muramasa-sensei.
It's from your beloved Izumi-sensei.
You're kidding!
I can't.
I can't!
Then I'll just hang up.
Don't!
S-Speaking!
Muramasa-senpai?
Yes, that is correct.
Wait, why are you speaking politely?
I-I mean, this is so sudden.
I was surprised, too.
I asked for your contact information,
and she said you were right next to her.
Were you in a meeting?
Oh, it doesn't matter, right?
Anyway, Masamune-kun,
you wanted to speak to me?
Well, there's going to be a Light-novel
Tenkaichi Budoukai wrap party at my place.
If you'd like...
...but you probably don't, right?
I'll go!
Why wouldn't I want to?
I'll go if I had to risk my life!
It's fine? I mean, the thing with me, um...
You idiot.
Just because I got turned down doesn't mean
my love for you will change so easily.
You really don't seem to understand me at all.
Of course I don't.
I've only met you three times so far.
You're right.
Then, once again...
My regards for the future, kouhai.
The pleasure is mine, senpai.
Coming!
Oh, hello. My name is Shidou Kunimitsu.
Is this Izumi Masamune-sensei's residence?
Oh, yes. I'm Izumi Masamune.
Oh, just as I thought!
It's a pleasure to meet you, Izumi-sensei!
No, the pleasure's mine.
Nice to meet you, Shidou-sensei.
Please, sit anywhere you'd like.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Shidou-sensei, you're the only one here so far.
I'll go make some tea.
- Um...
- Yes?
Why don't we drop the "-sensei" bit?
Oh, right.
Sorry to make you wait!
As you requested, I've become
the most beautiful girl in a yukata for you!
Masamune-kun, was this all right?
Y-Yeah. Perfect!
Shidou-kun is here already.
Who?
Pardon me!
I'll be right next to Masamune!
Hey!
You're being audacious!
Umm...
Yama-something-sensei.
Why do you only vaguely remember my name?
Then, Masamune-kun...
Are you listening!?
I'll take the other side.
D-Don't get so close like that.
Why are you so slovenly just for Muramasa?
I'm way cuter than she is!
Cute, not cute, that doesn't matter
when you're not dressed like normal—
Because a yukata—
That's enough!
There.
What was that?
A poltergeist.
Okay.
I-In any case, Izumi-kun,
you're really popular.
Huh? He's not popular at all.
Izumi-sensei already
has someone he's in love with, right?
He wouldn't be moonstruck
for anyone else, right?
Y-Yeah.
Your voice was rather soft.
Yes.
Yes!
I will not be moonstruck!
I'm going to get the food ready!
What kind of a relationship are they in?
Don't you be running away!
They have a lot going on.
A lot going on? But they're both guys, right?
I think he completely misunderstands us.
Masamune-kun, you made all this?
Yeah.
Whoa!
I hope it suits your tastes.
So tasty.
Then, enough with the introductions! Cheers!
Cheers!
Congrats, Masamune.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
Handmade?
Yes.
Tasty!
Thank you so much.
Come to think, your story
for the competition was about sweets, too.
I've always liked sweets ever since I was little.
Someday, I'd like to collaborate
with a food company.
My dream is to have characters or sweets
from my stories stocked up in stores.
Here, here!
My great dream is to write
the ultimate light-novel...
and conquer the world!
Before heading out into the world,
I have to first defeat Dengeki Bunko!
You mean me?
Starburst Stream!
Applause!
My dream is to write
the most interesting novel in the world...
...and to read it myself.
Well, I want to make the new title a smash hit,
and turn it into anime, and watch it here
together with my younger sister.
That is our dream.
That's a great dream.
Do your best.
Yeah!
And lastly, your turn, Eromanga-sensei.
My dream is...
Izumi-sensei already mentioned it.
You have one more, don't you?
What is your dream?
I...
...want to be the bride of the person I love.
Thanks for having us!
- Muramasa, let's go see fireworks!
- Huh? Sure.
Kunimitsu, you're coming, too!
Was the wrap party fun for you?
It was ordinary.
I see.
Everyone gathered here in this house.
Everyone ate the same food,
and talked about all kinds of things.
It was really fun for me.
On the other hand, now that everyone left,
it's all quiet now.
Nii-san...
Were you lonely?
That phone call the other day...
You were acting rather strange.
Yeah, I might have been.
You know, Sagiri, I...
I'm scared of being by myself.
Mom... my real mother...
got into an accident while I was home alone.
She never came home.
Ever since then, I've been scared.
So when I gained a new family, I was happy.
I'm so pathetic.
That's not true.
I lost the will to leave my room.
You alone being all right can't be the case.
Oh, it started.
I finally figured it out.
What you want is a family.
Yeah. I want a family.
I hadn't thought of you as family,
and I don't want to be your younger sister.
But, since you're so hopeless...
I'll pretend to be your younger sister for a bit.
夕焼けに染まる横顔, 騒がしい夏の鼓動
Yuuyake ni Somaru Yokogao, Sawagashii Natsu no Kodou
The color of the sunset graces your features:
A lively heartbeat of summer.
優しく髪をなでながら,微笑んだ君が切ない
Yasashiku Kami wo Nadenagara, Hohoenda Kimi ga Setsunai
I see you smile as the wind brushes your hair
And it breaks my heart.
わがままばかりでゴメンね, 今の二人で居たいなら
Wagamama Bakari de Gomen ne Ima no Futari de Itai Nara
I'm sorry for always being so selfish,
but if I want things to stay like this,
この気持ち 君を好きだって, まだ言わないよ
Kono Kimochi Kimi wo Suki Datte Mada Iwanai yo
I still can't tell you that I love you.
繋いだ指が　その愛しさが
Tsunaida Yubi ga Sono Itoshisa ga
The precious feeling of our joined fingers
胸の奥の花火みたいで
Mune no Oku no Hanabi Mitai de
Is like fireworks inside my heart.
もしも君もこんな私を受け止めてくれるなら
Moshimo Kimi mo Konna Watashi wo Uketometekureru Nara
If you'd be willing to accept me despite all this,
側に居たいよ
Soba ni Itai yo
Then I want to stay by your side.
I've gotten much further away.
Younger Sister
and the Fairy Island