You cooked all this yourself?
Yes, everything. Starting from the preparation.
Now, eat up!
I thought you were going
to show me how you work.
Right. As you can see,
I'm in the middle of working!
You're a novel author, right?
Just shut up and eat!
I named that "Spring Pixie's Full Nudity Soup"!
H-How is it?
It's amazingly tasty!
ヒトリゴト だ よ 恥ずかしい こと 聞かないで よ ね
Hitorigoto     da  yo    Hazukashii    Koto      Kikanaide     yo ne
I'm just mumbling to myself... don't ask me something so embarrassing!
キミノコトだよで もその先は　    言わないけどね
Kimi no Koto da yo Demo Sono Saki wa        Iwanai     kedo ne
It's about you... but I won't tell you any more than that!
Nii-sama subs presents:
掛け違えてる　ボタンみたいなもどかしさを
Kakechigaeteru      Botan    Mitaina       Modokashisawo
I'm so mixed up, like my buttons have been switched around.
ほどけないまま   また難しくしようとしてる
Hodokenaimama     Mata Muzukashiku Shiyou Toshiteru
Unable to figure it out, I'm just making things difficult again.
伝えたい  気持ちは 今日も
Tsutaetai     Kimochi wa Kyou mo
Once again, the feeling I want to tell you
言葉になる直前に　    変換ミスの連続で
Kotoba ni Naru Chokuzen ni  　Henkan Misuno Renzokude
Suffers a series of typos before it can even become words.
ため息と一緒に飲みこんだら　ほろ苦い…
}Tameiki  to Issho ni   Nomikondara　     Horonigai…
When I drink them down, along with my sighs, they taste so bitter..
ふとしたときに　探しているよ, 君の笑顔を　探しているよ
Futoshita Toki ni        Sagashiteiruyo,    Kimino Egao wo   Sagashiteiru yo
I'm searching before I even realize, I'm searching for your smile!
無意識の中　その理由は　まだ言えないけど
MuishikinoNaka　  Sono Riyuu wa       Mada Ienai Kedo
It happens unconsciously so I can't even tell you the reason why!
ひとりでいると　会いたくなるよ, 誰といたって　会いたくなるよ
Hitori     de  Iru   to　       Aitaku   naru  yo,   Dare to Itatte       　Aitaku     Naru  yo
Whenever I'm alone, I start wanting to see you! No matter who I'm with, I start wanting to see you!
たった一言　ねえどうして?
Tatta Hitokoto       Nee Doushite?
It's just one single phrase, so why is it...?
Aah 言えないその言葉　言えないこの気持ち　Aah
Aah...     Ienai    Sono Kotoba     　Ienai       Kono Kimochi   　Aah
Ahh... I can't say the words! I can't tell you this feeling! Ahh...
早く   気づいてほしいのに
Hayaku,        Kizuitehoshii      no ni
I just wish you'd hurry up and realize!
Thank you for that meal. It was tasty.
I'm a professional author,
so of course it would be.
The feeling of wanting to cook a meal
from scratch for someone who's on your mind.
Thanks to you, I understand how
the heroine thinks when she cooks for others.
I see.
I write novels as a hobby.
But hobbies you don't seriously play
are all boring, right?
Because it's a hobby, I put all my might into it!
I think I like cooking even more thanks to you.
All right!
Sagiri, this is from the neighbor, for you.
The neighbor's home-cooked meal
is really delicious.
Um...
Liar.
Me!?
This!
The neighbor?
We don't get along at all.
Is that me?
Here!
So erotic!
No! Don't you have something else to say?
Why do you only draw girls with small boobs?
Th-That's because...
Even if I give a request to make
the heroine's boobs bigger, you ignore it.
Um...
I'm...
I'm picky about the types of lewd art to draw.
I don't want to draw anything
I haven't seen in real life!
I-In real life...
Don't tell me that illustration from the other day was...
When you speak
of dreams, you should laugh!
Like this?
How outrageous!
Idiot! Lewd! Pervert!
You definitely just imagined me
doing really lewd things!
I bought those string panties
so I can draw that lewd illustration.
You're thinking I'm lewd!
I don't think that!
Not to that extent.
Lies!
Sagiri, listen to me!
An older brother doesn't think of lewd things
with his younger sister!
No matter how erotic you are,
it won't turn me on.
And moreover, I'd never make fun of you!
That's what an older brother is.
So stupid.
I don't care about or trust any older brothers
who are lewd liars.
Hey, can that be...
Is that our neighbor, Yamada-san?
"The neighbor? We don't get along at all."
Yee-haw!
"The neighbor's home-cooked meal
is really delicious."
Liar.
So that's what this is about.
It's true that I head over
to the neighbor's a lot lately.
But there's a reason for it.
What reason?
That's...
...something I can't say for now.
Liar.
Always, all the time, everything is a lie.
Nii-san...
Nii-san, I hate you.
I don't want to see your face.
Then, I'll prove that I'm not a liar.
For the past year, I've been thinking
about how I can get you
to recognize me as your older brother.
I finally get it now.
Sagiri, I...
I'll make my younger sister my heroine!
I'll write a light-novel
that's about my younger sister!
I'll write about my favorite thing in the world,
and create the ultimate light-novel!
I'm not happy about that one bit!
Not happy at all!
I'm not going to open up my heart
with anything like that! It's just gross!
I hate older brothers who are liars!
I don't trust you!
Hurry up and get out!
Let's do our best together next time, too!
Liar.
I'll do it.
With my max-fire motivation, I'll do what I can.
Several days passed. Before I knew it,
roughly two weeks were already gone.
I haven't seen Sagiri's face ever since.
Sensei, please do something about
the proposal for your new title by this week.
I'm sorry, but I'd like a little bit more time.
All right. Then take your time to think it out.
It's really scary to turn down work.
If I don't publish a new title,
my position disappears all too quickly.
Even the fans forget about me.
Two years ago, I wrote and wrote,
yet not one book was published.
I was losing heart,
and I'm about to be back in that state.
I'm fighting such fears, but still, I...
I wrote something interesting.
I have a good feeling about this.
It's open?
Yamada Elf-sensei? Are you here?
I hope you don't mind my intrusion.
Elf...
This is...
Oh, you were here?
Right. Today was the promised day.
Wait for me in the living room.
Got it.
Such a serious look on her face...
I've never seen it before.
Sorry to make you wait!
This is my new novel!
Chronicles of
Wandering Cat Girls
Yamada Elf
You said yesterday
that you haven't written one word of it yet!
With my ability "Summon Darkness",
I summoned a completed manuscript
from the demon realm!
I-Impossible! Such an ability!?
You thought I'd be surprised? You were
desperately writing that until moments ago!
I totally wasn't writing.
I totally summoned this from the demon realm!
If you think I'm lying,
you can check my laptop.
You erased it just for a stupid little trick?
Ya-Yamada Elf's new title...
B-But I'm Yamada Elf...
Besides, see?
The manuscript is right here.
Time for the showdown, Izumi Masamune.
I'll see through your little piece
with my God Eye!
Bring it on, Yamada Elf.
That novel you summoned
from the demon realm with all your might...
I'll have a read of it!
Interesting. It's tremendously interesting!
The hand keeps flipping the pages.
And my heart keeps wanting more!
Is this the true skills of an author whose works
get turned into anime?
On top of that, all the heroines
have small breasts.
There are so many poses that Eromanga Sensei
would love to draw.
And it's full of situations and outfits
that she might like!
And then...
It's super erotic.
It's tuned to be ultra-specialized.
This is a light-novel made for Eromanga Sensei!
You know, this...
Is this manuscript for real?
Well, Masamune?
This is very important. Answer me.
O-Of course, I'm dead serious.
I see!
What the hell is going on?
I can't...
I can't win against this.
So unfair!
Was my manuscript that interestin—
No! That's not what I'm talking about!
How dare you make me
read something like this?
Such... Such...
Was it that boring?
The one I wrote will sell ten billion times more!
But this...
I can't compete against this!
H-Hey!
What's up with you?
This manuscript wasn't written
to amuse a lot of readers.
You put your soul into this,
and wrote this just for one person!
Reading this crap of a manuscript
that is definitely not sellable,
the only ones who would get emotional
in this whole world would be myself, and
your younger sister, Eromanga Sensei!
H-How'd you find out?
It's pretty obvious after reading this.
Seriously?
It's like you plainly wrote here
that your younger sister is Eromanga Sensei.
I was planning on having
my younger sister read this novel.
Why don't you do that?
I think your thoughtfulness
will get across to her.
This super-duper-ultra-passionate
300 page love letter.
I was wondering what kind
of an exhibitionist you were.
But to think you weren't conscious of it.
I lost. I totally lost this one.
Wait, what are you doing!?
Why are you crying?
Such a lewd, amusing masterpiece...
Lost forever...
Well, thank you.
If it won't have those illustrations,
then there's no point in leaving it around.
Listen, I've lost,
but that doesn't mean you've won.
How are those different?
That's why you're so dense.
I'll win next time!
So, what are you going to do with that?
You won't say, "Nah, I'm not gonna
show this to my younger sister," are you?
I'll do it! I was planning on it anyway.
What are you planning to do?
Are you serious? If you fall, you'll get hurt!
Eromanga-sensei!
Sagiri! I'm coming for you right now!
Nii-san?
Well, this is, um, well...
Sagiri! I completed the manuscript
for my new piece! I want you to read it!
Well, I'm sorry.
It's okay now. But, it's not okay.
Why did you do something so dangerous?
Because you never opened
the door for me since that time.
Here.
What?
The reason I didn't open my door for a while.
This is...
Battle scenes. Have I gotten better
at drawing them?
It's almost like someone else drew them!
I see.
I watched videos of martial arts matches,
and read up on many references for weapons.
So that's why it's so...
But I don't like stories
with people getting hurt or dying.
That's from—
No, I've always been like that from before.
Don't get me wrong.
It's sad when the character you like
is no longer in the story.
That's why I've always resisted drawing that.
But, seeing face-to-face for the first time,
and talking about creating titles...
I felt it wasn't right
for me to just be good at drawing what I like.
Because I said you sucked...
I was really disappointed,
so I felt that I should fight as well.
Fight, as in, against me?
No. Look at this, too.
When I color it, it looks like this.
This is a version with a different hair style.
How is it?
You learned how to draw
characters with big boobs?
I got it to a level where I can barely get by.
She looks like this when stripped.
What do you think?
I think it's really erotic and very good.
I see. So for the past couple weeks,
you were practicing this.
Izumi-sensei.
Do you understand now?
It's impossible to drop me
from working on your new title.
What do you mean? Who said that?
I mean, you were hiding something from me.
You were secretly meeting
with our neighbor, Yamada-san.
You seemed to have fun.
You'd never meet anyone like that
outside of your job.
Since you started seeing her,
you seemed really motivated.
I thought, she must be your new illustrator.
So I cooped myself up
in my room and practiced.
Sagiri...
Izumi-sensei said his younger sister
was going to be his heroine.
He said he was going to create
the ultimate light-novel.
I was actually happy about that,
and that's when I thought I had to draw
the illustrations for it, no matter what.
I'm never, ever going to lose!
I won't hand over Izumi-sensei
to someone like that!
That's my line.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Yamada-san next door is the popular author,
Yamada Elf-sensei.
Yamada Elf-sensei...
Yes. Sh-She's a huge fan of Eromanga Sensei,
and wants to work together with her.
So we engaged in a novel duel,
with Eromanga-sensei at stake.
What? I didn't hear about this.
I didn't want to tell you.
Because I was afraid to be told you'd rather
work with a popular author instead of me.
I was scared.
Impossible! Nii-san, you really are an idiot!
I think so, too.
I have to tell you in the end, anyway.
That's not what I mean!
That's exactly how—
Enough.
I'm sorry but, I've already defeated her.
I won!
That's amazing.
To think you'd win against her...
Izumi-sensei, you're amazing!
Actually, we were going to have you
read both and decide.
No need for that.
From the start, I've already decided.
Let's keep working together
from now on, Izumi-sensei!
The pleasure is all mine, Eromanga-sensei.
I don't know anyone by that name.
Untitled
Izumi Masamune
Let me read this.
R-R-R-Right. Y-Y-Y-Yeah.
Why are you flustered?
I'm not flustered! No, not flustered one bit!
Hurry up.
Y-Yeah.
Please read it!
Then, I'll be over there—
No. Stay here.
N-No good. I might die from shock.
S-Sagiri?
Y-Yes?
H-How was it?
U-U-Um...
I think it's really interesting!
Really!?
It's just...
You can't publish it as a book like this.
I can't have anyone else read this.
It's so embarrassing.
Y-You're right. That's right.
Nii-san...
I'm...
I'm in love with someone.
I-I see.
Right. That's how it should be.
Because we're siblings.
I decided that I was going to be her family.
Got it.
単純な言葉　重ねてゆく　もっと心は素直で
Tanjun Na Kotoba  Kasaneteyuku   Motto Kokoro Wa Sunao De
Simple words continue to flow as you grow more honest with yourself.
なんでもないような　その笑顔が　明日を照らす光に
Nandemo Nai You na Sono Egao ga Asu wo Terasu Hikari ni
That smile that hides all your troubles is a light that will illuminate your tomorrow.
ずっと気づいていたんだって　この手に抱えていたんだって
Zutto Kidzuite Itan datte Kono te ni Kakaete Itan Datte
I've noticed all along! I've been holding it tightly in my arms!
弾けた　声に　流した　答えが　今　そっと　きっと　願いこめた
Hajiketa Koe ni Nagashita Kotae ga Ima Sotto Kitto Negai Kometa
An answer escaped along with my excited voice. Right now, ever so gently, I'm sure a wish was held within.
ずっと　まわる　まわる　夢の中で　繰り返し　君と踊った
Zutto Mawaru Mawaru Yume no Naka de Kurikaeshi Kimi to Odotta
In an endlessly revolving dream, I danced with you again and again!
揺れる景色　道は続く　通り過ぎる風にふかれ
Yureru Keshiki Michi wa Tsudzuku Toorisugiru Kaze ni Fukare
As the scenes around us sway to and fro, the path leads on. We're blown along by each passing wind.
何度も　超えて行けるから　境界線　雲かき分け　手を伸ばした
Nandomo Koeteyukeru Kara Kyoukaisen Kumo Kakiwake Te O Nobashita
Again and again, We'll overtake as many boundaries as it takes!
We've pushed through the clouds to reach our hands on high!
涙は今　浮かぶ空に預けて　走り出すの
Namida wa Ima Ukabu Sora ni Azukete Hashiridasu no
Leaving our tears to the sky above, we'll run onward...
並んで　見つけた　輝く光を手に
Narande Mitsuketa Kagayaku Hikari wo te ni
We'll take this light in hand, which we found by standing side-by-side.
Oh, I see, I see.
So you got rejected.
What's with that stupid grin on your face?
Serves you right!
So? What happened after that?
After that...
You know, Sagiri...
I have a dream now, too.
Dream?
That's right, a really big dream!
I'll turn this manuscript into a book.
It's out of the question as is,
so I'll rethink it, and write a project proposal.
I'll have my editor approve it, too.
That's where it begins.
But I'll make sure to turn this into a book.
I'll amuse tons of people with it, and have them
love the main character and the heroine.
It'll get super popular, and make enough money
for us to easily live on our own.
And then, have it turn into an anime!
Is that your dream, Nii-san?
No, no. That's all preparation.
We'll buy a large LCD television
for the living room,
and get ridiculously expensive speakers.
And then we'll have
a magnificent cake, with candles.
I'll take you out of your room,
and we'll watch the anime together!
It'll be our anime, where I wrote the story
and you drew the illustrations!
That way, I think both of us
would have a lot of fun!
All the sad things will be blown away by it!
That's my dream. It's the goal I have to get to!
How is it? Isn't it amazing?
It won't help if I speak in a loud voice.
I see. This time, too, huh?
This time?
Sagiri, you...
You've always been like that, Izumi-sensei.
You always give me dreams.
That's great, Izumi-sensei.
Let's do it!
I'm not gonna let you
do something so fun all by yourself!
That's not a dream for you alone.
Let's make that our dream, together.
I'm a little hungry.
Right, right. I got it. Hold on for a bit.
Our first step towards our dream.
I don't think I'll ever forget about this day
for the rest of my life.
Let's Plan a Light-Novel with your
younger sister